All of these pieces of footage
that you're watching me overlay on this
video
here are mine,
and I'm embarrassed to look at them.
They make me cringe inside.
I can't believe how awful so many of them
are.
But the truth is,
I'm incredibly grateful to
that version of myself who put out
terrible content because it
was only being that person
that I could incrementally
make better content over the years.
This is a part of the content creation
journey that so many people are just not
willing to endure.
Anything you put out today will probably
be pretty shit,
and it will stay shit for quite a while.
But over time, all you need to do
is get a little bit better.
Like the same with any skill in life,
repetition is what takes you to the next
level.
It doesn't have to take as many years as
it took me to get better, which is
why I created my Short-Form Content
Mastery course.
I'm giving you the cheat codes, the hacks,
the systems, and the shortcuts to
producing much better content.
Where there's better content,
there's better leads.
Where there's better leads,
there's better customers.
Where there's better customers,
there's better results.
And better results, better content.
Better content, better leads.
You see where this is going. So
if you comment the word "content"
underneath, I'll
send you everything you need to get going.
And the cost of this course,
which isn't a lot,
it's a fully fledged business
expense.
So send the invoice to your accountant,
they'll take care of the rest.
Cheers.